Craig: You doing a job
was a one-time thing.
This is about me
making my own money!
Well, then go get a real job
like real people.
You've always known
who I am!
Yeah.
But I didn't know you'd also be
a shitty mother.
Got an idea for a job.
Uh, you know
what a hawala is?
No.
It's like an underground
Western Union.
So, have you heard of these guys
where you got to,
you know, move money
without people knowing?
What you're talking about --
It's dangerous.
Max: Hey.
Your mom owes Uncle Max
money,
but...she's not taking Uncle Max
very seriously.
So go tell your mom that Max
said time's up.
Don't worry.
That man is never
gonna bother us again.
Excuse me.
What's the deal here?
You the owner?Yeah.
We got orders
to confiscate your inventory.
What the hell
is this about?
Well, thisis your last chance
to save your pathetic ass.
I made a phone call.
Your bar got raided.
Another call next week,
it's your house.
I'm the one who's gonna be
haunting your --
[ Gunshot ]
Dude never shuts up!
The gun's a burner.
But, um,
I think I'll keep it safe.
Just in case.
♪♪
♪ She stares deeply
♪ Locked inside me
♪ Burnin' brightly
♪ One they know
that I cannot take ♪
♪ Waitin' for it all to begin
♪ Every night now, they'll win
♪ Come and meet my black hole
♪ Got a big black hole
♪ I've got a big black hole
♪ I've got a big black,
big black hole ♪
♪ Got a big black hole
inside of me ♪
♪ Got a
♪♪
Jesus Christ.
I can't believe this.
We got to throw him
in a dumpster somewhere.
He has the Liquor Board
raid my place this morning,
and he's dead
by tonight?
Feds are gonna be on my ass
before the sun comes up.
So then we bury him
in the desert.
They'll never
find him there.
Deran: Dead or missing,
it doesn't matter.
I'm gonna be cuffed
and interrogated
at the Federal Center
by tomorrow morning.
Then just don't say shit.
Chadwick's
got the gun, man.
Doesn't matter. We have
the bullet that killed him.
He can't connect that gun
to anything
without admitting
he was here.
What are you
talking about?
There's blood and DNA and shit
all over the wall.
We bleach.
Get the mops.You know what?
Chadwick can make up
any bullshit story he wants.
He's a cop.
Anybody's gonna believe him.
Not gonna happen.
Pope, get his car.
We double wrap him.
Tight.
And we bleach everything.
The walls, the floor,
the ceiling -- everything.
Let's go.
[ Door closes ]
[ Beeping ]
It's an older model.
It doesn't have government tags.
It's his personal car.
Hopefully no GPS.
His phone has GPS.
I have his phone.
Turn it off
and give it to me.
Are there, uh -- Are there
cameras in the alleyway?
No, but there's cameras
at the restaurant
on the corner
of Wisconsin and Cleveland,
would've seen him
coming in.
Alright, so we need
to get rid of this car,
but we can't be seen
driving it.
You want a truck?
Yeah, how fast
can you do that?
This time of night?
Pretty fast.
You got one of those
American doctors in Mexico?
Yeah.
Good.
We're gonna need him.
♪ 'Cause I never give up
and I never give in♪
♪ Oh, so strong♪
♪ Got the power
when I turn it on♪
♪ Yeah, I'm gonna get my fill♪
♪ Nothing's gonna stop me now
and nothin' ever will♪
♪ I got the power♪
[ Dramatic music plays ]
♪♪
[ Engine starts ]
We're good.
[ Grunts ]
Get the trunk.
Oh, shit, his phone
needs to be on.
And he needs
to be using it.
That way he's still alive
when he leaves here.
I don't have
his passcode.
We get his face out.
Let's use the face recognition.
Yeah, well, don't his eyes
need to be open for that?
Alright, well,
open his eyes, get --
I don't think it works
like that, ma--
-Is that thumb recognition?
-Yeah, okay.
-Well, get his hand out.
-Use his hand.
Get his hand.
-[ Grunts ]
-Alright.
Alright, I'll just
keep it unlocked.
-Good.
-He's got mail.
Alright, well, respond.
Something generic.
-Quickly.
-Alright, here you go.
Alright, let's go.
Close it.
Alright,
meet back at the spot.
Yeah, yeah, stay off Cleveland,
alright?
The cameras cannot see
your car there, alright?
And burn that shirt.
It's got blood all over it.
-Yeah.
-We got this. Let's go.
♪♪
♪ Machines are racing♪
♪ The body's aching♪
♪ The gas tops over♪
♪ A silent soldier♪
♪ We're always ready♪
♪ The system's steady♪
♪ Let's go♪
♪ Words are floating♪
♪ My mind's eroding♪
♪ There's no complaining♪
♪ Its always raining♪
Oh, come on.
He's got everybody.
♪ Let's go♪
[ Car door opens, closes ]
You got the money?
Yeah.
And two burners.
Phones off.
♪♪
[ Truck door opens, closes ]
[ Truck door closes,
engine starts ]
Craig: You can't trust
the cops, man.
Shit happens, alright?
♪♪
There's a spot
in San Ysidro off Exit 29.
Should be
about an hour away.
What about Chadwick?
Well, if things go right,
the shooting shouldn't
be tied to us or the bar.
Then we tell Chadwick
we don't need him anymore.
There's no upside
in offing a cop, Pope.
Sometimes things
have to be done.
Doesn't matter
who it is.
♪♪
Chadwick's the only one
who knows anything, man.
He talks, he'd be
hanging himself.
The guy's crazy.
Who knows
what he's gonna say?
The feds are onto him,
they're on to us.
He's the one that went rogue
and shot the dude.
J and Pope get this done,
and Chadwick walks as long
as he keeps his mouth shut.
Yeah, we'll see
if J's plan works.
J's plan is gonna work,
man, okay?
So just relax.Don't tell me to relax, okay?
I'm the one tied
to all this shit.
We were all there, man, alright?
All of us.
It wasn't just you.Yeah, Livengood
would still be alive
if it weren't for me.We are a family,
and we'll stick together,
so get that shit
out of your head.
God damn it.
[ Engine shuts off ]
Any trouble
crossing the border?
No.
You got the money?
You have his car, too?
It's in there.
He's in the trunk.
Give me the keys.
Both vehicles.
We need to make it
look drug-related,
uh, something
on the border.
Street gang, cartel-affiliated,
that kind of thing.
Like a deal gone bad?
More like a hit.
So who is it?
Does that matter?
Yes.
He's DEA.
[ Scoffs ] Adiós.
No, no, no. Wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
Hold up.
Hey.
Nobody you do business with
wants 10 grand?
Nobody wants that kind
of attention.
How about 20 grand?
Nobody?
You sure about this?
Come on.
What's it gonna take?
25.
And you're gonna have
a lot more driving to do.
There's a house in Otay Mesa
on this side of the border.
That's where
they'll meet you.
Linda:
Thanks for meeting me.
Yeah, well, it's nice.
They like to play together.
Baz is obsessed
with those swings.
Rah!
Baz, Jesus Christ.
You're gonna
break your neck.
Come on.
-Watch this, Baz.
-He's like a wild animal.
Yeah.
You got lucky
that Andrew's so calm.
So, about Max.
Uh, he comes in
around 4:00 most days.
He'll have
a couple drinks,
then he picks a girl
and he goes to the VIP room.
You think you could get me
into one of those rooms?
What do you mean?
I mean have him come in,
let him have his drink,
and then you just tell him
that Sinnamon or Jade
or whoever is waiting for him
in the VIP room.
No.
No, no,
he chooses who he wants.
He'll like to be chosen.
Look, it's $1,500
up front for you.
No, I-I-I got a certain lane
that I try to stay in.
You know what I mean?
I'm just doing this
to protect my kids.
That's all.
Same as anyone would do.
[ Sighs ]
♪♪
[ Sniffs ]
What's up?
Ah, J and Pope
still not back?
They called last night.
It's gonna take a little longer.
What are you doing here?
[ Gate buzzer ringing ]
Who's that?[ Beep ]
[ Phone thuds ]Is that Frankie?
Yeah, I told her to come by.
She found a hawala.
I figured you might
want to hear.
It's gotta be today?
Hey, man, if you
wanna sit around
and worry about shit
that we can't control, go ahead.
But I'm gonna try to bring
some more work in.
Morning.
Bad time?
No.
What's up?
I got a guy.
Does money transfers for big
players from here to L.A.
Up to $250,000
each transaction.
Well, he's probably sitting
on a lot more than that.
How much more?
At least four
or five times that.
These guys take money in
and they give it out.
If he can move a quarter
of a million on any given day,
he's gotta be keeping
more than that somewhere.
Yeah, a safe, building, truck.
Something.
Be like robbing a bank.
Man, we just gotta find out
where his bank is.
If you want to find out
where he keeps his,
I can meet with him
today.
We can check out the location.
You can follow me.
Today's not gonna work.
[ Scoffs ]
Okay, when?
We'll give you a call.
Hey, I'll talk to him.
I need this, too.
The sooner the better.
♪♪
[ Engine shuts off ]
I guess this is it.
Uh-huh.
Anybody looking
for our guy yet?
No, we're good.
[ Thud ]
♪♪
Alright, let's do this.
The doctor sent you?
No.
Dios me envio.
Claro.
Doctor.
Donde esta el?
In the back.
[ Speaks Spanish ]
He wants us to get it.
Look, I'm not gonna come
looking for you, Renn, okay?
I just want to know
where you are. That's all.
Call me back.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
[ Door closes ]
Hey, if you don't wanna
check out this hawala,
I will.
I can't just stew in this shit
all day, man, okay?
I'm in.
What?
Alright.
You know, if this shit
with Livengood goes sideways,
I think it'd be smart
to have some cash
to get the hell
out of here.
Alright.
Let's do it.
Figure out the location
of Frankie's meet.
If it looks like a place
where they'd be holding
the bank, then we hit it.
Alright, well, how do we find
the bank in the building?
Tracking device.
Put it in the cash that Frankie
gives them to launder.
If they hear a beeping
transmitter in the stack,
we're burned.
I know.
Give her a call.
Let's do this.
Alright.
Su mano.
What?
Cortarlo la mano.
[ Speaks Spanish ]
They want us to cut
off his hand.
Okay. Why?
Must be a calling card.
Sells the story.
Well, you better
get on it.
[ Sighs ]
♪♪
[ Grunts ]
[ Crack ]
♪♪
What about the car?
Seven miles further
down the road.
You'll be crossing
into Indian lands.
Leave his car on the side.
Hand on
the passenger seat.
Why there?
Well, they have
their own police, right?
No DEA or FBI
without their permission.
Their police will find it
when we tell 'em to.
♪♪
[ Speaks Spanish ]
Uno, dos, tres.
♪♪
I guess they're gonna drag him
under the border.
♪♪
Meeting's this afternoon.
That's as late
as I could get.
Where's the location?
10th and Mesa --
two-story building.
How much you thinking
about sending?
$30,000.
I worked it out with a friend
I trust in Costa Rica.
You have that?
We need to talk about
something first.
We'll figure out
a finder's fee.
No.
No fee.
I need to be cut in.
How much?
Half.
You know we're talking about
a million dollars in cash,
maybe even more, right?
This guy gets robbed,
he's gonna start looking
at new faces, mine first.
When that bridge burns,
I need to be gone.
For good.
The $30,000's damn near
all the money I have.
If the exchange goes bad,
I get caught,
I'm out all my money.
It's a lot of risk.
We're risking our asses
actually doing the job.
Last I heard,
prison isn't that great.
Fair compensation.
That's all I'm asking for.
Okay.
Alright, we'll, uh,
split it up equally.
How many?
With you, five.
♪♪
[ Engine shuts off ]
[ "Edge of Seventeen" playing ]
[ Knock on door ]
♪ And a melody
♪ Nothin' else mattered
♪ Just like
the white winged dove ♪
♪ Sings a song,
sounds like she's singin' ♪
♪ Ooh, baby, ooh, said ooh
♪ Just like
the white winged dove ♪
♪ Sings a song,
sounds like she's singin' ♪
♪ Said ooh, baby, ooh,
said ooh ♪
♪ The clouds never expect it
♪ When it rains
♪ But the sea
♪ Ever want something so bad
♪ You could taste it?
♪ Made the deadline
and you passed the test ♪
♪ Sabotage seems safer
than success ♪
♪ Put it off until tomorrow
♪ I've heard it all before
♪ But it's one on one
♪ One on one
♪ It's you and me
against the world ♪
♪ It's one on one
♪ I need some time to think
the whole thing over ♪
♪ You say you want
to save the world alone ♪
♪ I want to taste and test
the waters with you ♪
♪ It's not so easy
when you're on you own ♪
♪♪
-You ready, baby?
-Yeah.
-Let's have some real fun.
-Mm-hmm. You know it.
Yeah.
♪ No excuses,
I just want the truth ♪
Shit.
♪ Reputation
is a fragile thing ♪
♪ I know you know it
♪ Well, it's one on one
♪ One on one
♪ It's you and me
against the world ♪
♪ It's one on...
Everything I've got,
down to what can fit in a purse.
And you're gonna give it
to some rando in Costa Rica?
He's not a rando.
You're really gonna stay
down there?
Dollar goes far in that part
of the world.
You'll get bored,
come back.
No, I'm done.
I was looking for a way out,
and then you showed up.
♪♪
[ Sighs ]
Better safe, right?
Yeah.
♪♪
[ Cellphone chiming ]
It's his daughter.
He's supposed to be picking her
up from soccer practice.
He's late.
♪♪
[ Rock music playing ]
Is that the thing people use
to find their wallets?
Uh, this is, yeah,
but this is LBS.
GPS can locate
a building,
but if you want to know
what room inside that building,
the LBS can pinpoint
a location within 40 feet.
Here I was thinking
that J's the tech nerd.
I have a regular
that comes into my bar
MacGyvering this kind of shit
all the time.
Sent me a couple
YouTube clips,
and I figured
the rest out on my own.
Where's Frankie?
Oh, she'll be back.
She's just getting changed.
Changed?
Why's she
getting changed?
Yeah, I don't know, man.
It's what she does.
You know, she's really
gonna go and do that
Central America thing.
Yeah, well,
could be us one day.
Hey, you heard
from them?
No.
You know, it's kind of our fault
what happened to Frankie.
With what Smurf did
and all.
I tell you what,
we're definitely giving her
one hell
of a going-away present.
♪♪
Boom.
Not bad, man.
Not bad?
It's a goddamn work of art.
[ Up-tempo music playing]
[ Indistinct talking ]
Thanks, baby.
Come see me again.
Any time.
♪ And in his mind
♪ Sunglasses blind
♪ Losing track of time
♪ Pulling up to the home
♪ Rolling up a smoke
♪ He's left there alone
Where's Linda?
I just saw her leaving
when I was coming in.
[ Door opens ]
Hey!
What the hell?
You said
he was gonna be here.He was. He left.
You stole money from me.
You understand that?
I did what you asked me
to do, Janine,
but he -- he --
he knew something was up.
What did you tell him?
Look, I got kids
to protect, too.
What did you tell him?
♪♪
[ Turn signal clicking ]
Jesus.
What is this place?
Teamsters?
Longshoreman.
Buddy I used to hang with,
his dad got him in.
This is the one with
the tracking device in it.
It's tucked
inside the band.
Should get plenty of intel
inside.
You know, entrances, exits,
cameras, all that shit.
Yeah, we'll check the outside
while you're in there.
Okay.
♪♪
[ Beep ]
Security.
Yeah, if I had a million dollars
in a union hall,
I'd have security, too.
♪♪
[ Lock clicks ]
Welcome to Local 4904.
You have an appointment?Yes.
Who you here to see?
The wizard.
Any weapons?
No.
Tryin' to be
respectful, Miss.
I got hams for hands.
Gotta leave that here.
♪♪
You're good.
I'll let him know you're here.
Have a seat.
Thanks.
♪♪
Yeah.
Sounds good.
Pope and J are
on their way back.
They just got to
dump the truck.
Did it go well?
I don't know.
Yeah, she's not moving.
She's still at the front.
I'm guessing the bank is
nowhere near the front door.
♪♪
Okay, he'll see you.
Look, the freeway entrance
is only half a mile.
Two, three turns max.
We can be
out of here fast.
I'm thinking we can make
a distraction up front.
Get in through the back?Tactical gear?
Big guns.
Scare the shit out of them.
We need to figure out
how big this safe is
we're talking about.
We should prepare
for the worst.
Bring equipment.
I mean, hell, we could
hit this tomorrow, man.
Shit.
She's on the move.
I know.
Old bald guy in the back
of a union hall.
Security looks like they're
gonna let you into Altamont.
I've learned not to judge a book
by its cover.
I've learned not to judge
my clients.
Keeps me in business.
Sit.
$30,000.
To Costa Rica.
♪♪
No offense.
None taken.
♪♪
My Costa Rica guy's
in San Jose.
Is that okay?
Yeah.
♪♪
Okay.
Think of a password.
It can be anything.
I share it with my guy.
You share it
with your recipient.
The code matches,
they pick up the money,
minus my 5%.
"Freedom."
"Freedom" it is.
How soon?
Should be processed
later this evening.
Excellent.
The lads
will show you out.
Thanks.
♪♪
Think maybe we should
pick up the pace a little?
We're far enough away.
You watch TV?
Uh, no, not really.
I watched a lot.
You know, when I was a kid.
Nature shows mostly.
They kind of
calmed me down.
We were, uh...
never really kids.
Me and your mom.
But you were.
For a while, anyway.
You and me,
we're not the same, J.
Not like that.
[ Explosion ]
[ Tires screeching ]
♪♪
Hey, look, everybody.
Mommy's home.
I didn't want
to leave them.
Oh, Bree, it's fine.
Cousin Max always
shows up unannounced.
Really, it's fine.
Thank you, Bree.
Janine, you want to
come inside and talk?
Yeah.
Yeah, let's --
let's talk.
Uh, why don't you guys
play outside?
No. No, no.
I-I think
they should see this.
No, Max.
No.
Yeah.
Come on.
We're just gonna talk.
Alright, let's --
let's go in.
Let's watch some TV.
♪♪
Watch TV.
Sit down.
Guys, sit down.
Here.
[ Indistinct talking on TV ]
[ Clears throat ]
You want to try to tell me
why you were setting me up?
I just wanted to talk.
Lying is just gonna
make this worse.
No, really, I-I-I've been
thinking about some stuff,
you know,
high-level shit,
and, um, I wanted
to talk about how --
how we could make
some more money.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Me and you?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, doll?
Yeah.
Isn't so tough, right?
Hey.
[ Gasps ]
Lie to me again.Don't do this
in front of my kids.
Lie to me again. Come on.
One more's all I need.
Come on.
[ Choking ]
Listen.
Gonna kill me?
Is that what you were gonna do?
Huh?
Gonna try to kill me?
How's that feel?
What the hell is this?
That was really
not smart.
[ Gun clatters ]
[ Gasping ]
Want to see something?
No.
Okay, not in front of my kids.
Ah!
Ow! Ow!
Ow!
What'd you do that for?
God, you little shit.
[ Gunshot ]Ah! Ah!
Ah. Oh.
You shot me?
Ohh.
Ow.
Huh?
[ Groans ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
God.
Easy.
Look away.
[ Groans ]
You bi--
[ Body thuds ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
Hey, come here.[ Gun thuds ]
Come here.
It's okay.
Oh, God.
[ Breathing heavily ]
Frankie: His office
was right about here.
There was
an adjoining door.
Craig: Were those two dudes
the only security at the door?
Yeah, them and Wyatt
were the only three people
in the building
as far as I could tell.
Okay, so they only
do their business
when the place is closed.
Wyatt?
I spotted his business card
on his desk.
He's not very discreet.
Alright, so,
we, uh,
get to him first, then he can
bring us to the cash, yeah?
Yeah, sounds good.[ Clang ]
Ah, the boys
are back from war.
Frankie.
We're into
the hawala thing.
Frankie found us a big fish
not far from here.
Good.
Well, I should go home.
We can finish up tomorrow.
It's her contacts,
her cash.
Figure she's in on the job
with us if that's alright.
Yeah, all good.
Livengood?
We had to send the doc
an extra 15K, but it's handled.
They just need
to find him now.
♪♪
[ Exhales deeply ]
Alright, got these.
You okay?
I changed the license plate
to a dummy,
put bullshit papers
in the glove compartment.
We'll make sure
that nobody can find him.
Did, uh, the neighbors
hear anything?
Bree's the closest.
I'll talk to her.
Alright.
Let's go.
I should come.
Nah,
stay with your kids.
Look,
it was self-defense.
It's not like
you planned it.
[ Car door closes ]
I can come back.
I'm fine.
Okay.
[ Engine starts ]
Jesus Christ.
♪♪
And then she's gone?
So she says.
It's a big haul.
A million or so.
Guy works out of
a union building.
Not totally sure
where the cash is,
but I figure
we all go back,
take a look
before we finalize a plan.
How do we find out
where the money is?
I put a little mini
GPS tracking device
in the cash
that Frankie gave him.
[ Cellphone chimes ]
Oh, shit.
What?
The money's not at
the union hall anymore.
It's on the move.What?
Says it's about 10 miles
from here, but it's moving.
Okay. Well, then wait
for it to land.
No, no, we follow it.
Find out how it's being moved
and where it's going.
♪♪
Andrew, hey, get ready
for the best chili
you've ever had in 10 minutes.
Are you okay?
Here.
That good, huh?
[ Sighs ]
Did you close your eyes
when I asked you to?
Why not?
You didn't
close yours.
He was a bad man,
right?
Yeah, baby.
Yes, he was.
You did good.
Okay?
Hey.
[ Clatter ]
Now, don't lose that.
♪♪
How far behind it
were we?
About a mile.
I think it turned
down another road.
J: Is it still stopped?
Yeah.
♪♪
It's been still
for a minute now.
This way.
♪♪
Jesus.
It's huge.
Can you tell where the signal's
coming from?
Yeah, south side
of the port.
Dude's a longshoreman.
Makes sense.
Secure.
These places
are like Pendleton.
Worse.
It's easier
to break into Fort Knox.
Tons of security
since 9/11.
Yeah, Customs,
Coast Guard, cops.
Deran:
Yeah, we'll figure it out.
We make a plan,
and we follow it.
That's what we do.
Right?
♪♪
Let's get to work.